[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Speaker 1: Hi, my name is Bail Dixon.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Hi, Bail.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] How can I help you?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Speaker 2: I signed up for the app for the first time.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I've been a PetSmart customer for decades, but I made an order and for some reason it shipped to the address not on file with my order but to my Apple Pay, like my billing address.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] And I was trying to see if the order had shipped and if there is any way to get it shipped to the correct address.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] And then I was trying to understand why that happened so it doesn't happen again because it didn't let me review it.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I didn't see a review page of the order.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I guess it just went.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] And I used Apple Pay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] So I was wondering if Apple Pay interfered with it or what happened because I checked my address on file with you that I signed up with only one address that I entered in my app.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I didn't even enter the other address at all, so I don't know where it pulled that other address from.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Okay, let me help you with that.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] So first, could you please confirm your phone and email?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Sure.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] My phone is 434-547-3198.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] And my email, I think I have VailDixon at gmail.com.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] V is in Victor.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] A-I-L is in Lima.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] D-I-X-O-N is in Nancy at gmail.com.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Thanks so much for the information.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Okay, could you please confirm me the chipping address?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: The one that was used or the correct one?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] The correct one.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 1407 Theodore T-H-E-O-D-O-R-E Street in Killdevil Hills, North Carolina, 27948.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Actually, that's the shipping address.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] What could happen in this case?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Have you paid with Apple Pay?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] It's really important that the moment that you complete the process for the payment, you let us know that it's a different dealing for chipping address.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] But for this order, we're going to chip the package to the corporate address.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] So are those digital scratchers?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Yes.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Okay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: I don't know why on the app it says it was shipping to another address.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] It still said it.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I don't know how it even got that address because I didn't type it in anywhere.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] But it pulled it somehow.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Oh, maybe it could be Apple Each.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Do you worry?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] The order will be shipped to the address beginning 1407.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] The other is true.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Okay, great.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Because I thought that's what I had entered as the security dress.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] And then after the confirmation page, it showed, and even when I went back into purchase history, it shows it is shipping to 2370 Buffalo Station Drive and in another state.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] So that's great.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] The second question I had was when I signed up for the app, I do have a rewards account with you, and it seemed to pull my points.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I wasn't sure it was really linking with the right phone number.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I wanted to make sure it was pulling in my account into the app into the new online account that I created.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I used to have an online account, but it must have deleted it a long time ago.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I think I might have.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I've always had a reward number, so I'm not sure.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] But did it pull my history in?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Did it pull my purchase history in?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I couldn't see my purchase history, but it seemed to maybe pull my points.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Yep, they already.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] The order is under your Truth Reward Points, so you will receive your points.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Remember, after the purchase, it could take 72 hours and you will see your points, but the order was pressed under your Truce Reward account.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Oh, yes, I understand this one was, but I was wondering if when I signed up for the app, did it pull in all of my previous points with my phone number that was linked to my account, the one I use in the store all the time?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Because I had purchased like thousands of dollars of stuff, so I wanted to make sure those points were pulled in.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Well, under these accounts that I can't see.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Yep, the points are right there.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] You're a BIPP member from BitSmart.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] So yep, all the points that you receive at the moment that it pictures a dessert are in your account.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Okay, how many points can you see?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: The moment the points that you have available, 3,087 points.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Okay, and what do you do with the points?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Usually when I go at the store, they just say you have this many dollars of rewards.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Do you want to use it?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: And I say, yep.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Is that what it converts into is rewards dollars?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Yep.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Okay, is there anything else you do with points?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] No?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Okay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I didn't know how it worked.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Awesome.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: I'm so glad I can maybe there is something else that I can execute right now.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] I think that's all.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Thank you so much.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: You're very welcome.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Thank you.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Thanks so much for calling BitCommerce.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Thank you.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] You too.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Are they a good company to work for?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Yes.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Thanks so much for calling.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Bitsmore.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Have a good day.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Okay, bye.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Bye-bye.